Guide to the Lewis and Clark Centennial and American Pacific Exposition and Oriental Fair Records 1894-1933
Oregon Historical Society, Research Library
- Publications, Series 12
  - General Publications
    - Lewis and Clark Bill of Fare (menu), circa 1905 (Box-folder 101/22)
    - Message of Governor James K. O'Toole to the Eighth Legislative Assembly of the State of Montana, 1903 (Box-folder 101/23)
    - The Music Trade Review, circa 1905 (cover article on the exposition) (Box-folder 115/5)
    - Oregon booster, 1905 August 3 (Box-folder 115/15)
      Magazine, including photographs of state buildings and article on Princess Trixie, the educated horse
    - The Oregon Mist (newspaper, St. Helens, Or., with promotional information about Columbia County), 1905 July 28 (Box-folder Oversize Folder)
    - Schubert Club of Seattle—Program, 1905 (Box-folder 101/24)
    - Souvenir of the Bancroft Free Home for Consumptives, 1905 (Box-folder 101/25)
    - A Souvenir Song and a Welcome, poem by Alson Landon Woodward, circa 1905 (Box-folder 115/8)
    - Story of the Televue, 1905 (Box-folder 101/26)
    - St. Louis Post-Dispatch, 1904 Oct. 23 (Box-folder Oversize Folder)
      Contains articles on demolition of St. Louis exposition buildings; and "How I Photographed the World's Fair" by Jessie Tarbox Beals.
    - Traveler's Aid Association of Portland —Report, 1905 (Box-folder 101/27)
    - Universal Exposition, St. Louis, Rules and Regulations Governing the Aeronautical Competition, 1904 (Box-folder 101/28)
    - The Whole Dam Family (cartoon) and The Weekly Initiative (newspaper, Portland, 1905 May 2) (Box-folder 123/13)
- Scrapbook of General Charles Beebe, circa 1905; Series 13 (Box 102)
  Contains invitations to General Beebe and his wife for events related to the exposition, and related ephemera. Also includes unrelated clippings regarding early U.S. History.